Hello Hello friends welcome to lines from the so
today we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance and
its strengths and losses for
shift way Yadav so let's know
directly on our chart so
this chart has been opened I have opened my head wash
account if you do
n't have your demat account yet then
I have given the link in the description below and from that chart
if you want then through our link you will be
able to open your demat account absolutely free and from there you will be
able to start your trading so let's talk
first of all what happened on Friday in ICICI General Insurance so
you can see here
and
even in the coming days the thing to be worried about here is that
till now
what support is right for many and research from is being made, we will
definitely bring it to you by asking here
and here on today's side
we feel that it may happen
now let's see our results there it is going to be available
in the coming days
so open here  Keep it done, it
is available here and you are
getting small amounts in both, so
subscribe, if you want to
remember or you
cannot trust it again, do
subscribe,
whenever we target anyone, then
now as far as my friend is concerned,
in this topic for the coming days, then
write current, for the coming days, whatever it can
give us here in the negative, to
what extent can it give, if I say 278
or butter 28th, definitely see in the comment box, after
talking about the government, you can get
mostly 71215 here, so do a little work in the world,
first of all, I have
definitely taken a positive 2015, subscribe here a
lot
so that you can
definitely get it here in the coming days by commenting, but
if you subscribe to our channel,
press the bell icon of our channel and turn on the
notification because if you have
not done all the notifications for yourself, then here
when you bring everyday videos for all of you by
adding the post office,
you will mix that which we bring everyday for
videos, which we bring after the market opens
Tell me 12 hours in advance that the next day, that is, in the
morning, what can we
see online till the closing of the next day,
only in the comments,
we tell about it on the basis of the entire chart, so
you must have missed it there,
because of this, do not forget to press the bell icon
and turn on the notifications, the rest goes to
our one-hour charts and
there we will talk about what we are going to see for the market in this disease, so
here
I would first of all submit the support and register of any important thing which is
in any form, so
the
way I am marking here, you should
return to your chart exactly to the same
because all these places will
help in deducing your target and stoploss,
so definitely go here, do
not
forget to do this marking at all, here I am not for much, I am
forgiving only as much as we need for this Friday for the agricultural market, the
rest is already applied, that is,
for responding, we already have marketing software.
That was it, I would just watch the new data for some time,
I would just select that and keep the rest of
our marking here, now let's talk about
closing according to that, 3019
more director here, our
806 here, remember
sexual
hatred, it means
school, so here you should not do it at all from home on
any one side,
then see the information,
if you do not know then
I have set n targeting surgical
video here and definitely share, when you watch that video,
there I have told you how you have to see the
confirmation grand, how you have to maintain
your target and stop loss,
along with that, if
our stock should go down in intraday or from up,
how you can make profit in intraday,
so definitely
when you watch this video completely, now
here in my friend's stock, Monday is
important, give support and here I will
tell you, subscribe here
3834, after that here
I have given two supports and here you
must
subscribe and
definitely subscribe to my channel, which is of positive side  I
think chances are being made in stock on Monday,
especially positive Singh got 3026 to
34th, I think good action can be seen in work, one can get
arrested moments from this time,
let's know, you will get to
see in your eyes, if you want to see clothing among the writers of 32 days,
it
means my love for positive for an hour, did
you in stock for Monday, do
tell us by commenting, if you
liked our end nice, then please
like our video, share it and do
not forget to subscribe to our channel,
thank you, it has happened